<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Ben Kulbertis</title>
    <link>http://ben.kulbertis.org/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Ben Kulbertis</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 23 Mar 2016 16:36:34 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://ben.kulbertis.org/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Changes in mod_authz_unixgroup from Apache 2.2 to 2.4</title>
      <link>http://ben.kulbertis.org/2016/03/changes-in-mod-authz-unixgroup-from-apache-2-2-to-2-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Mar 2016 16:36:34 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ben.kulbertis.org/2016/03/changes-in-mod-authz-unixgroup-from-apache-2-2-to-2-4/</guid>
      <description>mod_authz_unixgroup is an Apache module that can be used to allow members of Unix groups on the server to access restricted content with their Unix user credentials. These groups are defined in a Require directive and therefore it can be used with essentially any AuthType. We utilize this extensively at my place of work, as all our users and groups are stored in our Active Directory, which are then mapped to Unix users and groups on all our machines via pam_ldap.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Synchronizing A MySQL Database with Git and Git Hooks</title>
      <link>http://ben.kulbertis.org/2011/10/synchronizing-a-mysql-database-with-git-and-git-hooks/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Oct 2011 19:19:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ben.kulbertis.org/2011/10/synchronizing-a-mysql-database-with-git-and-git-hooks/</guid>
      <description>When I develop web based projects I often use a MySQL database to hold the data for my project. I also use git for source control and since I tend to work on my projects from several different computers I push and pull from a VPS of mine. This system works great for keeping all my source code in check and is easily accessible. However, I have had one issue. I was having to create a testing instance of my MySQL database on every computer that I pulled onto and worked from.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>